Finding Aid for American Society for Information Science and Technology Records, 1925-2001
University of Michigan Library (Special Collections Research Center)
- ADMINISTRATIVE
  - Chapter and SIG files, [1987-1988] (Box 20)
  - Chapter files, 1968-1976 1978-1981, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Committees
    (see also Committees series)
    - Committee Administration, 1984 (Box 20)
    - Committee Reports, 1983-1984 and 1989-1990 (Box 20)
    - Committee Files, 1969-1977 1988-1990 1992-1993, 5 folders (Box 20)
      (includes material on SIGs and chapters)
  - Complaints, 1980-1989, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Computer Systems
    - Computer search, 1984-1985 (Box 21)
    - Computer Enterprises, Inc. (CEI)
      - Financial (Box 21)
      - Documentation Masters
        - Report Generator, 1990 (Box 21)
        - Screens, 1990 (Box 21)
        - Financial Statement Reporting, 1990 (Box 21)
        - Database Management, 1990 (Box 21)
        - Meeting Management, 1990 (Box 21)
        - Accounts Payable, 1990 (Box 21)
        - Code Tables, 1990 (Box 21)
        - General Ledger, 1990 (Box 21)
    - CWS Office Systems, 1981-1982 (Box 21)
  - Constitution and Bylaws
    - Published versions, 1951-1968 (Box 21)
    - Bylaw Revisions, 1956 1966-1970 1984, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Copyright law and auxiliary publications, 1938 (Box 21)
  - Council
    - Council Handbook: Summaries of Action, undated (Box 21)
    - Other files, 1968-1976 (Box 21)
  - Development Effort, 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - Directory listings, 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - Elections
    - Ballot forms, 1981-1983 (Box 21)
    - Ballots and related, 1986-1988, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Biographical Information: on officer candidates, 1968-1979 (Box 21)
    - General, 1981-1986, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Electronic Mail System
    - Compmail, 1984 (Box 21)
    - General, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Executive Director's and Secretary's reports, 1952-1963, 2 folders (Box 21)
    (includes quarterly and annual reports)
  - Executive Director's Working Papers: notes and miscellanea, 1985-1986 1989 1994 and undated, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Focus Groups
    - Focus Group Task Force, 1988-1990 (Box 22)
    - General, 1988-1990, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - General Correspondence, 1972-1980, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Goals and Objectives
    - Five Year Plan, 1985 and undated (Box 22)
    - Survey, 1981 (Box 22)
  - Guide to People and Services, 1985-1992 (Box 22)
  - Handbook and Directory (Handbook & Directory), 1965 1967-1968 1981 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Headquarters Activity, ca. 1978 (Box 22)
  - Headquarters Bulletin, 1970-1972 (Box 22)
  - History of ASIS
    (see also Irene Farkas-Conn Historical and Research Files series)
    - Society Activities, 1968-1975, 4 folders (Box 22)
    - Master's Thesis by Angela Lynn Dierking, 1975 (Box 22)
    - ASIS historical sketch, 1985 (Box 22)
    - ASIS Landmark Events, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Insurance
    - Group Insurance Plan for Members, 1967-1976 and undated, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Indemnification, 1984 (Box 22)
    - Insurance Benefits, 1964 1966-1985 1987, 10 folders (Box 22)
    - Liability Insurance, 1982 (Box 22)
  - Job Descriptions, 1974 (Box 22)
  - Legal Correspondence
    - Copyright, 1964-1977 (Box 23)
    - Corporate, 1987 (Box 23)
    - Lobbying, 1976 and 1986 (Box 23)
    - Pension, 1971-1972 (Box 23)
    - Taxation, 1963-1981, 3 folders (Box 23)
    - Trademarks, 1967-1977, 2 folder (Box 23)
    - Wage-Price Freeze, 1971 (Box 23)
    - Washington and Lee, 1975 (Box 23)
    - Miscellanea, 1960-1980, 3 folders (Box 23)
  - Logo, 1967-1971 (Box 23)
  - "The Management of ASIS: A Planning Discussion between Council and the Operations Planning Task Force (OPTF)," 1978 (Box 23)
  - Manual: "Headquarters Policy and Procedures"
    - Draft, 1975, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Approved version, 1976 (Box 23)
    - Updates, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Membership
    - Kudos, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
    - Promotion, 1987 (Box 23)
  - Memos, Office, 1971-1982 (Box 23)
  - Mergers: ADI and STWP (Society of Technical Writers and Publishers), 1964 (Box 23)
    (see also Special Libraries Association Merger series)
  - Miscellanea, undated (Box 23)
  - Mission Statement, undated (Box 23)
  - Name Changes, 1963-1968 (Box 23)
  - Office Diary, 1981-1986, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Organizational Structure Task Force
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1979-1980 (Box 23)
    - Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 23)
  - Personnel
    - Executive Director Performance Review, 1988 (Box 23)
      [Restricted until 2063; removed to box 188]
  - Policy Manual
    - 1979, 3 folders (Box 23)
    - 1984-85, 1 folder (Box 24)
  - Policy Statement: drafted by Manfred Kochen, 1977-1978 1982 and undated (Box 24)
    (including 1982 update)
  - President's Address, 1956 ? (Box 24)
  - Presidents' and Executive Directors' Files
    (many files collected by past executive directors or presidents and later sent to ASIS to complete the historical record; includes correspondence, reports, pamphlets, etc.)
    - Karl F. Heumann, 1938-1970 (Box 24)
    - Eugene Jackson, 1952-1962 (Box 24)
    - John Kaiser, 1956-1970 (Box 24)
    - Simon Newman, 1959-1960, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Presidents of ASIS, 1962-1967 (Box 24)
  - Press Releases, 1937 1944 1973 1976 1984-1989, 8 folders (Box 24)
  - Publicity/Public Relations, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
    (includes some press releases)
  - SIG Files, 1977-1981 (Box 24)
  - Simon Newman Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Site Development
    - Site selection, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
    - Office space selection, 1990 (Box 24)
  - Society Activities: alphabetical by topic
    (compiled for Claire Schultz by Sheryl Wormley?)
    - A, 1968-1975 (Box 24)
    - M-, 1968-1975 (Box 24)
  - Team ASIS: staff development workshop, 1990 (Box 24)
  - Technical Programs, 1976 (Box 24)
  - Watson Davis Obituary, 1967 (Box 24)
  - Weekly reports by Robert McAfee, 1974-1980, 4 folders (Box 24)
    (see also executive directors' monthly reports/memoranda in Council)
- CORRESPONDENCE
  The CORRESPONDENCE series (11 linear feet) is made up of three subseries: the Early Leaders File, the Chronological File, and the Alphabetical File.
  The Early Leaders File consists of correspondence to and from some of the early leaders of ADI/ASIS, including founder Watson Davis, Robert C. Binkley, and Vernon Tate, as well as materials from officers in the 1950s and 1960s, when ADI underwent its shift and expansion from a documentation institute to a professional society concerned with all aspects of the emerging discipline of information science.
  The Chronological File subseries is based on an ASIS office file originally created by Robert McAfee, who served as assistant executive director from the early 1970s through the early 1980s. After McAfee left in 1982, the Chronological File was continued by succeeding ASIS officers and staff. It consists primarily of the correspondence of executive directors and deputy executive directors. It also contains correspondence from other ASIS staff and Board members. Much of this material is outgoing correspondence that includes supplementary material such as meeting minutes, brochures and scholarly papers. Because of the large number of attachments, the Chronological File offers a good representation of the functions and activities of ASIS as a whole, and not just its communications via its correspondence. Much of the correspondence from the 1990s was routine in nature (e.g. conference speaker confirmations, dues notices, donor thanks, etc.); most of this was discarded, with some samples kept.
  Finally, there is an Alphabetical File subseries. This is another ASIS office file with the earliest material beginning in 1962. The bulk of this correspondence is from Joshua Smith's tenure as Executive Director (1973-1976). It also includes some attachments.
  - Early Leaders File
    - Watson Davis, 1937-1952 (Box 25)
    - Robert C. Binkley, 1938-1939 (Box 25)
    - Vernon Tate, 1947-1948 (Box 25)
    - Simon Newman, 1951-1954 (Box 25)
      (includes other materials besides correspondence: minutes, reports, etc.)
    - John B. Kaiser
      (includes other materials besides correspondence, e.g. notes, drafts of letters, reports, pamphlets, other documentation;)
      - Topical files
        (headings supplied by processor)
        - Budget Committee problems, 1961 (Box 25)
        - Executive Director's reports and correspondence, 1961 (Box 25)
        - Office memorandum and correspondence, 1960 and 1962 (Box 25)
        - Retirement, 1962-1964, 2 folders (Box 25)
          (includes other topics)
        - Subscriptions procedures problems, 1961 (Box 25)
        - Working papers and correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 25)
      - General correspondence, ca. 1951-1974, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Karl Heumann
      (includes other materials: reports, minutes, etc.)
      - ca. 1953-1958 (Box 25)
      - 1954-19561959-19611964 and undated, 14 folders (Box 25)
        (includes many items [copied to Heumann] to and from other ADI leaders such as Vernon Tate, Cloyd Dake Gull, Robert Binkley, and others)
    - Cloyd Dake Gull, 1960-1963 (Box 25)
    - Claire Schultz, 1962 (Box 25)
    - Other Names, 1938-1939 and 1950 (Box 25)
  - Chronological File
    - Robert McAfee
      (includes some materials of other persons, in particular Samuel Beatty)
      - 1970-1975, 9 folders (Box 25)
      - 1976-August 1982, 13 folders (Box 26)
    - Samuel Beatty and John Brokenshire
      (includes some materials of other persons, notably a substantial amount of material from Nancy LeFebvre, her position unknown)
      - October 1982-December 1984, 22 folders (Box 26)
      - January 1985-1986, 8 folders (Box 27)
        (1986 incoming only)
    - Bonnie Carroll, 1980-September 1986, 21 folders (Box 27)
      (includes some materials of other persons)
    - Linda Resnik
      - March -1985-November 1986, 31 folders (Box 28)
      - December 1986-December 1988, 31 folders (Box 29)
      - January -February 1989, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Dick Hill and Peter Solomon
      (includes some materials of other persons; some [later?] files are just Dick Hill's and not Peter Solomon's)
      - Outgoing correspondence: Peter Solomon, 1988-1990, 3 folders (Box 30)
        (includes some incoming correspondence)
      - March 1989-November 1990, 25 folders (Box 30)
      - December 1990-December 1991, 25 folders (Box 31)
      - January 1992-April 1993, 30 folders (Box 32)
      - May 1993-July 1994 and November 1994, 22 folders (Box 33)
      - January, March -April, June -December 1995, 13 folders (Box 33)
      - March -June, September -October 1996, 3 folders (Box 33)
      - July -December 1997 (Box 33)
      - March, June -September 1998 (Box 33)
      - February 1999 (Box 33)
  - Alphabetical File, 1962-1981
    - A
      - General, 1971-1976, 3 folders (Box 34)
      - Atherton, Pauline, 1970-1972 (Box 34)
    - B
      - General, 1972-1975, 3 folders (Box 34)
      - Baker, Dale B., 1973-1976, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Becker, Joseph, 1968-1973 (Box 34)
      - Bryan Dinner, 1970 (Box 34)
    - C
      - General, 1968-1975, 5 folders (Box 34)
      - Cretsos, James M., undated (Box 34)
    - D
      - General, 1968-1978, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Day, Melvin, 1975-1976 (Box 34)
      - Drexel Institute, 1963-1964 (Box 34)
      - Duke University Conference, 1966 (Box 34)
    - E
      - General, 1972-1976, 3 folders (Box 34)
      - Elias, Arthur, 1965-1975 (Box 34)
      - Exhibits, 1973-1974 (Box 34)
    - F
      - General, 1971-1975, 3 folders (Box 34)
      - FID, 1975 (Box 34)
      - Fischer, Margaret, 1974 1977 (Box 34)
      - Foreign Contacts, 1970-1971 (Box 34)
      - Funding Possibilities, 1974 (Box 34)
    - G
      - General, 1973-1975, 3 folders (Box 34)
      - GPO, 1970-1972 (Box 34)
      - Grosch, Audrey N., 1977-1978 (Box 34)
    - H
      - General, 1972-1975, 3 folders (Box 34)
      - Hanson, Arthur B., 1975-1977 (Box 34)
      - Herlitz, Steven K., 1964-1965 (Box 34)
      - Herrmann, Roy, 1975 (Box 34)
      - Historical Collection, 1962-1973 (Box 34)
      - Hughes, Robert, 1974 (Box 34)
    - I
      - General, 1971-1975 (Box 34)
    - J
      - General, 1973-1975, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - K
      - General, 1973-1975, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Koller, Herbert R., 1973-1974 (Box 35)
      - Kyle, Robert, 1966-1972 (Box 35)
    - L
      - General, 1972-1975, 3 folders (Box 35)
      - Landau, Herbert B., 1979-1980 (Box 35)
      - Landau, Robert, 1970-1971, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Lunin, Lois, 1971-1975, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - M
      - General, 1972-1975, 3 folders (Box 35)
      - Maginnis and Associates, 1981 (Box 35)
    - N
      - General, 1972-1975, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Newman, Simon, 1970-1976 (Box 35)
    - O
      - General, 1972-1975, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - P
      - General, 1972-1976, 3 folders (Box 35)
      - Papier, Lawrence, 1970 (Box 35)
      - Price, Douglas S., 1974-1975 (Box 35)
    - Q
      - General, 1974 (Box 35)
    - R
      - General, 1972-1976 (Box 35)
    - S
      - General, 1973-1976, 5 folders (Box 35)
      - Sherrod, John, 1971-1973 (Box 35)
      - Svenonius, Elaine, 1980-1981, 4 folders (Box 35)
    - T
      - General, 1974-1975 1978, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Taylor, Robert, 1967-1969 (Box 35)
    - U
      - General, 1973-1974 (Box 35)
    - V
      - General, 1971-1975 (Box 35)
    - W
      - General, 1972-1976, 3 folders (Box 35)
      - Weil, Ben, 1973-1974 (Box 35)
      - White, Herbert S., 1973-1977, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Wiley and Sons, 1976-1981 (Box 35)
      - Williams, Martha, 1976-1977 (Box 35)
    - X, Y, Z
      - General, 1973-1975 (Box 35)
- CHAPTERS
  The CHAPTERS series (22 linear feet) includes the records of groups of members located within a well-defined geographic area and approved by Council. Student Chapters are affiliated with a specific school of library and information science and are located under the heading "Student Chapters." This series contains general material from the Chapter Assembly and the Officers Workshops, in addition to Chapter Memos, Chapter of the Year Awards documentation, Chapter Officer Manuals, and financial information specifically regarding the chapters. A small amount of chapter financial information can also be found in the Financial series. The bulk of this series is an alphabetical arrangement of chapters by name (except that Student Chapters are grouped at the end of the list), which include their minutes, constitution and bylaws correspondence, newsletters, Chapter of the Year Award nominations and financial information. Some Chapter of the Year materials can also be found in the Awards series.
  - Activity Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - Boundaries, 1966 (Box 36)
  - Bylaws and Proposed Changes, 1964-1982 and undated, 4 folders (Box 36)
  - Chapter Assembly
    - Advisory Committee, 1980-1986 (Box 36)
    - Award of Merit, 1981-1986 (Box 36)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 36)
    - Councilor Reports, 1973-1981 (Box 36)
    - Deputy Assembly Chairman, 1976-1977 (Box 36)
    - Director Reports, 1981-1982 1987 (Box 36)
    - Duties of Councilors, 1977-1978 (Box 36)
    - Minutes and Agendas, 1962-1985 1999, 8 folders (Box 36)
    - Nominations Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 36)
    - Student Chapter of the Year, 1985 (Box 36)
    - Tear Sheets, 1974-1981 (Box 36)
    - General, 1972-1991, 5 folders (Box 36)
  - Chapter Challenge Survey, 1994, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Chapter Development Fund, 1983-1986 1988 (Box 36)
  - Chapter Development Fund Ad Hoc Committee Report, 1982 (Box 36)
  - Chapter Lists, 1975-1982 (Box 36)
    (includes contact persons lists)
  - Chapter Memos
    (includes attachments)
    - 1973-1978, 3 folders (Box 36)
    - 1979-1988, 6 folders (Box 37)
  - Chapter Newsletter Editors Workshop, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Chapter of the Year Award
    - Correspondence, 1974-1986 (Box 37)
    - Miscellanea, 1975-1980 and 1990, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Nominations and Jury Committee, 1976-1982 (Box 37)
    - Purpose and Checklist, 1975-1979 (Box 37)
    - Selection Criteria, 1976-1980 and undated (Box 37)
    - Statements, 1977-1984 (Box 37)
    - Tear Sheets, 1977-1980 (Box 37)
  - Chapter Officers' Manual, 1966-1979 and undated, 7 folders
    - Correspondence, 1963-1976 and undated (Box 37)
    - Manuals, 1976 1979 (Box 37)
    - Miscellanea (Box 37)
  - Chapter Officers Workshop
    - Agenda, 1963-1980 (Box 37)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1982 (Box 37)
    - Minutes, 1963-1978 (Box 37)
    - General, 1974-1984 (Box 37)
  - Committees: regarding Chapter of Choice, 1981 (Box 37)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - Undated and 1961-1973, 4 folders (Box 37)
      - 1974-1998, 20 folders (Box 38)
    - Dissolution of Florida and Missouri Chapters, 1973-1977 (Box 38)
  - Financial
    - Annual Financial Reports
      (see also Financial Statements and Individual Chapters financials)
      - Reports, 1972-1986 (Box 39)
      - Correspondence regarding, 1966-1980 1987, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Audit Preparation, 1969-1978 1990, 3 folders (Box 39)
    - Bonding of Chapter Treasurers, 1978-1980 (Box 39)
    - Chapter Finance Summary, 1972-1973 1991-1992, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Chapter Project Fund, 1974-1979 (Box 39)
    - Chapter Project Grants, 1965-1969 (Box 39)
    - Chapter Rebates
      - 1963-1983 1985-1991 1994-1998, 24 folders (Box 39)
      - 1999, 4 folders (Box 40)
    - Chapter Remittances, 1971-1972 1981 1987, 3 folders (Box 40)
    - Chapter Treasurers, 1979 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1983 and undated (Box 40)
    - Financial Report Charts, 1970-1976 (Box 40)
    - Financial Statements, 1976-1977 1981 1983-1984 1987-1992 1995-1997, 15 folders (Box 40)
      (see also Annual Financial Reports and Individual Chapters financials)
    - Guidelines for Program and Financial Planning, 1974-1978 (Box 40)
  - Lending Agreement, 1976 (Box 40)
  - Membership, 1979 (Box 40)
  - Membership Procedures, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Miscellanea, 1966-1985 (Box 40)
  - Motions, 1975-1981 (Box 40)
  - Newsletters, 1982-1987 1990-1992, 5 folders (Box 41)
    (includes correspondence)
  - Officers, 1963-1989 1992-1994 1996-1998, 8 folders (Box 41)
  - Policy Statements, undated (Box 41)
  - Procedures
    - Chartering and Dissolving Chapters and Student Chapters, 1973-1981 (Box 41)
    - Voting, 1979 and undated (Box 41)
  - Prospect Tracking System, 1989 (Box 41)
  - Publications, 1971-1973 (Box 41)
  - Questionnaires
    - 1963 and 1979 (Box 41)
    - "Essence of Chapters", 1985 (Box 41)
  - Slide Show on Information Science, 1979-1980 (Box 41)
  - Speakers Bureau
    - Correspondence, 1966-1980 (Box 41)
    - Hot Topics, 1974-1980 and undated (Box 41)
    - Reports, 1974-1981 (Box 41)
  - Starter Kit for New Chapters, 1974 1984-1986 1988, 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Student Chapters
    - Advisors, 1975-1984 (Box 41)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1983 1987-1989 1992-1998, 5 folders (Box 41)
    - General, 1964-1985 (Box 41)
    - Officers' Manual, 1984 (Box 42)
    - Possible New Chapters, 1964-1982 (Box 42)
    - Seed Money, 1992 1995-1996 and 1997-1998, 3 folders (Box 42)
  - Telephone Call Record, 1974-1975 (Box 42)
  - Individual Chapters
    ("Financial Reports" and "Financial" includes chapter income statements, finance-related correspondence, and information about chapter rebates)
    - Alabama, 1976 (Box 42)
    - Arizona and New Mexico
      - Financial, 1998 (Box 42)
      - General, 1974-1980 1998-1999, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Australia, 1973-1974 (Box 42)
    - Baltimore, 1970 (Box 42)
    - Canada: Possible Chapters, 1963-1969 (Box 42)
    - Carolinas
      - Annual Activity Report, 1976-1981 (Box 42)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1973 (Box 42)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1981, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Financial, 1973-1980 (Box 42)
      - Membership, 1973-1981 (Box 42)
    - Central New Jersey
      - Chapter of the Year, 1977-1985, 5 folders (Box 42)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1975-1985 (Box 42)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1985, 3 folders (Box 42)
      - Financial, 1977-1985 (Box 42)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1976-1984 (Box 42)
      - Membership Directory, 1980 (Box 42)
      - Minutes, 1976-1980 (Box 42)
      - Newsletters, 1977-1984, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Officers, 1976-1984 (Box 42)
    - Central Ohio
      - Annual Reports, 1975 1981-1983 (Box 42)
      - Bylaws and Constitution, 1976-1985 (Box 42)
      - Chapter of the Year, 1976-1989, 5 folders (Box 42)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1987, 7 folders (Box 43)
      - Financial, 1970-1986 1991-1999, 5 folders (Box 43)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1965-1982 (Box 43)
      - Minutes, 1976-1987, 4 folders (Box 43)
      - Miscellanea (Box 43)
      - Newsletters, 1964-1984, 8 folders (Box 43)
      - Officers, 1970-1985 (Box 43)
      - Tear Sheets and Reports, 1973-1979 (Box 43)
      - Telephone Call Record, 1975 (Box 43)
      - General, 1985-1995, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Chesapeake Bay
      - Annual Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1978 (Box 43)
      - Financial Reports, 1968-1979 (Box 43)
      - Newsletters, 1972 (Box 43)
      - Officers, 1968-1973 (Box 43)
    - Chicago
      - Annual Reports, 1967-1981 (Box 43)
      - Bylaws, 1962 (Box 43)
      - Chapter of the Year, 1977-1985, 4 folders (Box 43)
      - Chicago Online Users Introductory Guide, 1976-1978 (Box 43)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1985, 3 folders (Box 44)
      - Financial, 1967-1986 1991-1993 and 1995-1999, 3 folders (Box 44)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1976-1986 (Box 44)
      - Membership Directory, 1979 1982, 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Minutes, 1981 (Box 44)
      - Newsletters, 1974-1985, 5 folders (Box 44)
      - Officers, 1970-1984 (Box 44)
      - General, 1981-1987 1989 1991-1995 (Box 44)
    - Colorado Centennial
      - Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 44)
      - Bylaws, 1979 (Box 44)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1984 (Box 44)
      - Financial Reports, 1979-1985 and 1993, 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Newsletters, 1979-1983 (Box 44)
      - Officers, 1979-1980 (Box 44)
      - Tear Sheets, 1979-1980 (Box 44)
      - General, 1984-1985 1988-1989 1991, 3 folders (Box 44)
    - Connecticut Valley, 1973-1974 (Box 44)
    - Delaware Valley
      - Annual Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 44)
      - Chapter of the Year, 1975-1976 (Box 44)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1964-1981 and undated (Box 44)
      - Correspondence, 1959-1982, 4 folders (Box 44)
      - Executive Committee, 1976 ? (Box 44)
      - Farewell Party for Stella Keenan, 1974 (Box 44)
      - Financial, 1966-1986 1991-1993 and 1995-1999, 5 folders (Box 44)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1960-1983, 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Membership, 1973-1976 (Box 44)
      - Minutes, 1966-1978, 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Newsletters, 1964-1984, 5 folders (Box 45)
      - Officers, 1962-1984 (Box 45)
      - Online Workshop, 1975, 2 folders (Box 45)
      - State Activities and Governor's Conference, 1976 (Box 45)
      - Tapes, Cassette: regarding Objectives, 1975 (Box 45)
      - Tear Sheets and Press Releases, 1975-1979 (Box 45)
      - Telephone Call Record, 1974-1977 (Box 45)
      - General, 1972-19751988-1989, 3 folders (Box 45)
    - East Tennessee
      - Annual Report, 1976-1985 (Box 45)
        (includes support material)
      - Chapter of the Year, 1980-1982 1987-1988 (Box 45)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 45)
      - Directory of Information Professionals, 1988 (Box 45)
      - Financial, 1976-1986 1991-1998, 4 folders (Box 45)
      - Meeting Announcements, 1974-1981 (Box 45)
      - Newsletters, 1979-1985 (Box 45)
      - Officers, 1975-1982 (Box 45)
      - General, 1985-1989 1992-1995, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - England, 1969-1979 (Box 45)
    - European
      - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 45)
      - Financial, 1998 (Box 45)
      - General, 1974 1985-1987 1991-1997 1999, 3 folders (Box 45)
    - Florida